Okay, it's lame when I say it,
it's ridiculous when you pile on.
(Leonard:)Okay. Sorry.
(Penny:)What did she say
when you told her we were going out?
LEONARD:
Um....
(Penny:)You didn't tell her we were going out,
did you?
LEONARD:
Um....
(Penny:)-Why not?
-Um....
(Sheldon:)Leonard,
I'm no expert on meditation...
(Sheldon:)...but if you're trying to calm yourself
down, I believe the word is "om."
(Beverley:)It was so nice of you
to come to the airport to pick me up.
(Sheldon:)No trouble at all.
(Leonard:)I drove, Mother.
(Leonard:)I'm driving now.
(Beverley:)Yes, dear. Mommy's proud.
(Beverley:)Thank you for your notes on my paper
disproving quantum-brain-dynamic theory.
(Sheldon:)My pleasure.
You know, for a non-physicist,
you have a remarkable grasp...
(Sheldon:)...of how electric dipoles
in the brain's water molecules...
(Sheldon:)...could not possibly form
a Bose condensate.
(Leonard:)Wait, wait, wait. When did you
send my mom notes on a paper?
(Sheldon:)August 16th.
Right after her carpal-tunnel surgery.